字幕制作 by 露易娘
那是什么？
What was that?
没有什么。
Nothing.
好吧，给我一点提示。
Okay, just give me one little hint.
不，没有提示。
No, no hints.
我们快到了。
We're almost there.
好吧，我要把它摘下来。
Okay, I'm going to take this off.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
嘿，你说你喜欢惊喜。
Hey, you said you like surprises.
是的，我愿意。
Yeah, I do.
当我知道它们是什么时。
When I know what they are.
你会爱它。
You're going to love it.
我保证。
I promise.
是的，我已经很喜欢景色了。
Yeah, I already love the view.
嗯。
Uh-huh.
你好？
Hello?
有燃烧的火车。
There's a burning train.
燃烧的火车。
A burning train.
好吧，我们...
Alright, we're...
你停下了什么？
What's your stop?
我看不到。
I can't see.
好吧，停下来。
Alright, stop.
我正在脱掉...
I'm taking it off...
现在。
now.
我什至不知道这个地方还开放。
I didn't even know this place was open yet.
拉起了一些帮助，让我们进入了开幕之夜。
Pulled some favors and got us on the list for opening night.
哦！
Oh!
你确定我穿好衣服吗？
Are you sure I'm dressed all right?
你看起来像一百万美元。
You look like a million bucks.
快点。
Come on.
它燃烧，燃烧，燃烧。
And it burns, burns, burns.
火环。
The ring of fire.
嘿！
Hey!
不要从喷泉中窃取积分。
Don't steal points from the fountain.
运气不好。
It's bad luck.
抱歉，先生。
Sorry, sir.
继续。
Go on.
微笑。
Smile.
这是你的票。
Here's your ticket.
谢谢。
Thank you.
大家好吗？
Did you catch that, everyone?
你来吗？
You coming?
取下一个。
Take the next one.
噢，来吧。
Aw, come on.
我们可以适合您。
We can fit you in.
谢谢。
Thanks.
上升。
Going up.
哦，对不起。
Oh, excuse me.
抱歉，有时会这样做。
Sorry, it does that sometimes.
有关斯卡格威塔的事实。
Facts about the Skagway Tower.
它高494英尺，重9,000吨。
It's 494 feet tall and weighs over 9,000 tons.
它由钢和钢筋混凝土和玻璃制成。
It's made of steel and reinforced concrete and glass.
更令人印象深刻的是，整个项目已经完成了史克威（Skagway）五个月。
And even more impressive, the entire project was completed five months out of Skagway.
这不是一件好事。
It's not a good thing.
这是一件好事。
It's a good thing.
什么时候。
What a time.
哦，很抱歉，我们已经结束了。
Oh, I'm sorry, but we're already over.
开放之夜的能力，我们无法容纳您。
Capacity for opening night, we cannot accommodate you.
如果您不介意我们辞职。
If you wouldn't mind us stepping aside.
太感谢了。
Thank you so much.
没关系，我和杰克一起工作了。
It's okay, I worked it out with Jake.
他在这里吗？
Is he here?
我可以和他说话。
I could speak to him.
我们今天早上让杰克去。
We let Jake go this morning.
太感谢了。
Thank you so much.
这是怎么回事？
What's going on here?
一秒钟，一秒钟。
One second, one second.
哦，先生。
Oh, sir.
我是一个非常重要的人，但也许您可以帮助我。
I'm a very important man, but maybe you could help me out.
拜托，你把我撕裂了。
Please, you're tearing me apart.
但是对不起，我无能为力。
But I'm sorry, I can't help you.
如果您不介意。
If you wouldn't mind.
哦，富勒先生，很高兴见到你。
Oh, Mr. Fuller, how nice to see you.
我们有一张可爱的桌子。
We have a lovely table for you.
谢谢。
Thank you.
这样，请。
This way, please.
让我们去酒吧。
Let's go to the bar.
我很自然。
I'm natural.
等待几个。
Wait a few.
什么？
What?
我害怕身高。
I'm scared of heights.
哦，不。
Oh, no.
我以前从未如此高。
I've just never been this high up before.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
这个晚上真是一场灾难。
This night's such a disaster.
我真的希望它是完美的。
I really wanted it to be perfect.
嘿。
Hey.
这是完美的。
It is perfect.
因为我和你在一起。
Because I'm with you.
啊。
Ah.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我想我会活的。
I think I'll live.
是的。
Yeah.
嘿，看，免费香槟。
Hey, look, free champagne.
那是我最喜欢的。
That's my favorite kind.
我可以运行吗？
Can I run it?
好的。
Okay.
我马上回来。
I'll be right back.
对不起，女士们在哪里？
Excuse me, where's the ladies room?
舞池的另一侧。
Other side of the dance floor.
谢谢。
Thank you.
嗨，亲爱的。
Hi, sweetie.
一切好吗？
Is everything all right?
我很好。
I'm fine.
谢谢。
Thank you.
你走多远？
How far along are you?
什么？
What?
哦，不。
Oh, no.
不，我不是。
No, I'm not.
我不知道。
I don't know exactly.
也许一两个月。
Maybe one or two months.
这是个好消息。
That's wonderful news.
不是吗？
Isn't it?
我还没有告诉我的男朋友。
I haven't told my boyfriend yet.
他爱你吗？
Does he love you?
是的。
Yes.
那他不会放手。
Then he won't let go.
谢谢。
Thank you.
当然。
Of course.
再见。
Bye.
好的。
Okay.
快要结束了。
It's almost over.
哦。
Oh.
嘿，什么？
Hey, what?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
是的。
Yeah.
我认为是这样。
I think so.
快点。
Come on.
让我们来一些新鲜的空气。
Let's get some fresh air.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
不用担心。
Don't worry.
我想...
I wanted to...
你先去。
You go first.
好的。
Okay.
我要给我们吃晚饭。
I was gonna do us a dinner.
但是看到我们有这种观点...
But seeing as we have this view...
嘿。
Hey.
不要扔那一分钱。
Don't throw that penny.
你可以杀死一个人。
You could kill somebody.
哦，我很抱歉。
Oh, I'm so sorry.
当然。
Of course.
是的。
Yeah.
法斯斯。
Fatass.
一...
Um...
过去的几年...
These past few years...
我绝对是神奇的。
I've been absolutely magical.
那就是嗯...
And that's, uh...
那是因为你。
That's because of you.
虹膜...
Iris...
我想和你一起度过余生。
I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
你的意思是...
You mean...
和我们在一起？
With us?
什么？
What?
对不起。
Sorry.
我...
I...
我是世界上最幸运的人。
I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
什么？
What?
你不沮丧吗？
You're not upset?
你在开玩笑吧？
Are you kidding me?
不，这是...
No, this is...
这是不可思议的。
This is incredible.
真的吗？
Really?
我们要建立一个家庭。
We're gonna start a family.
周围，​​所以...
Um, so...
你会？
Will you?
是的。
Yes.
啊!
Ah!
一...
Um...
太紧了吗？
Is it too tight?
这是完美的。
It's perfect.
嘿。
Hey.
让我们清醒。
Let's go sober.
住口。
Shut up.
不！
No!
出色地...
Well...
我意识到矢量乘法是可怕的，但这并不令人恐惧。
I realize vector multiplication is scary, but it's not that scary.
好吧，今天就是这样。
All right, that's it for today.
我们将开始为下周的最后一个准备。
We'll start prepping for the final next week.
雷耶斯女士！
Ms. Reyes!
我们需要谈谈。
We need to talk.
不要扔那一分钱。
Don't throw that penny.
你可以杀死一个人。
You could kill somebody.
哦，这个梦想破坏了我的生活。
Oh, this dream is ruining my life.
我也是我的。
Mine too.
每天晚上，斯蒂芬...
Every night, Steph...
天哪，我没有睡觉。
God, I'm not getting any sleep.
该死，对不起。
Shit, I'm sorry.
一...
Um...
我可以告诉你一些事情吗？
Can I tell you something?
是的？
Yeah?
这是怎么回事？
What's up?
所以在我梦中的女人，她的名字叫虹膜，对吗？
So the woman in my dream, her name is Iris, right?
好的。
Okay.
那是我祖母的名字。
That was my grandmother's name.
我，嗯，我想我在梦见她。
I, uh, I think I'm dreaming about her.
你是认真的？
Are you serious?
是的。
Yeah.
事情是，我什至从未见过她。
The thing is, I never even met her.
我什至不知道她是否还活着。
I don't even know if she's alive.
好吧，好...
Okay, well...
要么回家，了解奶奶，并希望能阻止梦想，要么留在这里死在您的睡眠中。
Either go home and find out about Grandma and hope that stops the dreams, or stay here and die in your sleep.
真正的。
For real.
因为我会谋杀你。
Because I will murder you.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
是的，好的。
Yeah, yeah, okay.
爱你。
Love you.
我也爱你。
Love you too.
回家。
Go home.
悄悄。
Quietly.
嘿，她是。
Hey, there she is.
嘿，爸爸。
Hey, Dad.
欢迎回家，亲爱的。
Welcome home, sweetie.
我很高兴你在这里。
I'm so glad you're here.
是的，我也是。
Yeah, me too.
我知道。
I know.
很高兴见到你。
So great to see you.
谢谢，谢谢。
Thank you, thank you.
嘿，对不起。
Hey, sorry.
查理（Charlie）前一段时间带了您的房间，我的文件在他的房间里，所以我为您裁员。
Charlie took your room a while ago, and my files are in his room, so I made up the pullout for you.
可以吗？
Is that okay?
是的，是的，不，这听起来还不错。
Yeah, yeah, no, that sounds totally fine.
嗯，嘿，我们还有那盒妈妈的旧东西吗？
Uh, hey, do we still have that box of Mom's old stuff?
它有一些照片，例如通讯录。
It had, uh, some photos, like an address book.
它是电话号码。
It's phone numbers in it.
嗯，你为什么要那个？
Uh, why do you want that?
哦，这没什么大不了的。
Oh, it's not a big deal.
我只是，我以为我看到它躺在这里的某个地方。
I just, I thought I saw it lying around here somewhere.
斯蒂芬妮，这是怎么回事？
Stephanie, what's going on?
好的，这听起来真的很奇怪，但是我，嗯，我只需要找到妈妈的妈妈，艾里斯。
Okay, this is gonna sound really, really weird, but I, uh, I just need to find Mom's mom, Iris.
嗯，好吧。
Uh, okay.
是的，这很奇怪。
Yeah, that is weird.
而且你知道，妈妈离开后，我已经摆脱了几年前的盒子。
And you know, I got rid of those boxes years ago, after Mom left.
哦，嗨，查理。
Oh, hi, Charlie.
嘿。
Hey.
一个，嗨，斯蒂芬。
Um, hi, Steph.
你好吗？
How are you?
很高兴见到你。
It's so nice to see you.
是的，当然。
Yeah, sure.
嗯，去表亲吗？
Uh, going to the cousins?
哇，现在？
Whoa, now?
看，你姐姐刚回到家。
Look, your sister just got home.
我以为我们可能...嗯...
I thought we might, uh...
实际上，你知道吗？
Actually, you know what?
我可以，我可以开车。
I can, I can drive you.
无论如何，我想见到他们。
I was wanting to see them anyways.
没关系。
That's fine.
嘿，如果您要见到表亲，请不要谈论Iris。
Hey, if you're gonna see your cousins, please don't talk about Iris.
不要出去。
Don't go out.
是的。
Yeah.
是的，没问题。
Yeah, no problem.
好的。
All right.
再见，爱你。
Bye, love you.
我也爱你。
Love you, too.
查理？
Charlie?
你能把这些取出来吗？
Can you just take these out, please?
我想和你说话。
I'm trying to talk to you.
你有什么问题？
What's your problem?
什么？
What?
您整个时间都没有说什么。
You haven't said anything this entire time.
什么？
What?
斯蒂芬，你为什么在这里？
Steph, why are you here?
我的意思是，我只是回家度假。
I mean, I'm only coming home for holidays.
我必须告诉你一些事情。
I have to tell you something.
但是你必须保证不要告诉爸爸。
But you have to promise not to tell Dad.
你怀孕了吗？
Are you pregnant?
不，我没有怀孕，查理。
No, I'm not pregnant, Charlie.
我不知道。
I don't know.
那不是...
That's not...
我的意思是，你在上大学。
I mean, you're in college.
你能保证我不会告诉爸爸吗？
Can you just promise me you won't tell Dad?
我为什么要告诉爸爸？
Why would I tell Dad?
很认真，查理。
It's serious, Charlie.
好的。
Okay.
一...
Um...
我正在接受学术缓刑。
I am on academic probation.
哇。
Whoa.
停止！
Stop!
如果我不取得成绩...
If I don't get my grades up...
对我来说，这是一个重要的时刻。
This is kind of a big moment for me.
这有点有趣。
This is kind of funny.
您是班主任，Valedictorian小姐。
You're a class president, Miss Valedictorian.
如果我不提高成绩，我将失去奖学金。
If I don't get my grades up, I will lose my scholarship.
哦。
Oh.
我俩，对不起。
I'm both, sorry.
发生了什么？
What happened?
我睡不着。
I can't sleep.
每次我闭上眼睛时，我都会对Iris进行同样的反复噩梦。
Every time I close my eyes, I have this same recurring nightmare about Iris.
我们的祖母。
Our grandmother.
我不...
I don't...
我的意思是，这必须意味着什么。
I mean, it has to mean something.
我不知道。
I don't know.
我梦见奇怪的事情。
I dream weird things.
昨晚我梦见一只热狗吃了我。
I dreamed a hot dog ate me last night.
就像，热狗在吃我。
Like, the hot dog was eating me.
好的。
Okay.
啊!
Ah!
杜德，你能做点什么吗？
Dude, can you just do something?
只需移动一点即可。
Just move a little bit.
我必须看着下面。
I have to look underneath.
给我一个好意。
Do me a kindness.
你还记得昨晚发生了什么吗？
Do you remember what happened last night?
这是怎么回事？
What's going on?
我找不到paco。
I can't find Paco.
伙计，再次？
Dude, again?
谁是paco？
Who's Paco?
嘿，因为。
Hey, cuz.
哦，天哪，嘿，你能帮我们看吗？
Oh my gosh, hey, can you help us look?
只要看着你的脚步。
And just watch your feet where you're stepping.
是的，当然。
Yeah, yeah, sure.
我必须先和你父亲说话。
I gotta talk to your dad first.
你他妈的在家吗？
What the fuck are you doing home?
哦，伙计，她他妈的出学。
Oh, dude, she's fucking out of school.
嘿，欢迎来到俱乐部。
Hey, welcome to the club.
埃里克（Eric），杜德（Dude），你在任何地方看吗？
Eric, dude, have you looked anywhere?
Paco不在楼上。
Paco's not upstairs.
哦，但是看谁在这里。
Oh, but look who's down here.
嗨，朱莉娅。
Hi, Julia.
哦，天哪。
Oh my gosh.
嗨，本。
Hi, Ben.
查理。
Charlie.
有我的小罗密欧。
There's my little Romeo.
因此，我们不得不与Jenny-Go一起舞会。
So, we had to prom-pose him with Jenny-go.
她说是的。
She said yes.
哦，天哪。
Oh my gosh.
谁是珍妮？
Who's Jenny?
哦，他在初级救生员中遇到了她。
Oh, he met her in Junior Lifeguards.
初级救生员？
Junior Lifeguards?
查理，我不知道你在做初级救生员。
Charlie, I didn't know you were doing Junior Lifeguards.
好吧，你要穿什么？
Okay, so what are you gonna wear?
我只是要简单。
I'm just gonna keep it simple.
黑色西装外套。
Black blazer.
是的，是的。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
斯蒂芬妮！
Stephanie!
哦，天哪。
Oh my gosh.
嗨，亲爱的。
Hi, honey.
您在这里需要多长时间？
How long are you here for?
不久。
Not long.
霍华德叔叔周围吗？
Is Uncle Howard around?
是的，他回来了。
Yeah, yeah, he's up back.
我给他。
I'll get him.
霍华德！
Howard!
斯蒂芬妮在这里。
Stephanie's here.
进来。
Come in.
伟大的。
Great.
你看起来有点累。
You look a little tired.
一切好吗？
Is everything okay?
斯蒂芬妮！
Stephanie!
看你！
Look at you!
来这里，来这里。
Come here, come here.
哦，亲爱的。
Oh, sweetie.
哦，很高兴见到你。
Oh, it's so good to see you.
嘿，你饿了吗？
Hey, are you hungry?
我要吃午饭。
I was gonna make some lunch.
不，实际上，我来这里是因为我想和你谈谈你的母亲。
No, actually, I came here because I wanted to talk to you about your mother.
虹膜。
Iris.
我知道你不喜欢谈论她。
I know you don't like to talk about her.
没什么可说的。
There's not much to tell.
嘿，孩子们，来吧，午餐！
Hey, kids, come on, lunch!
只是我一直对她进行了反复发生的噩梦。
It's just that I've been having this recurring nightmare about her.
哦，亲爱的，这可能只是一种压力。
Oh, honey, it's probably just a stress.
您应该尝试褪黑激素。
You should try melatonin.
好的，但是很奇怪的是，我一直梦想着50年前的一个真正的地方。
Okay, but the weird thing is, I've been dreaming about a real place from 50 years ago.
就像一家名为Skyview的餐厅。
It was like a restaurant called The Skyview.
你知道这是什么吗？
You know what it is?
艾里斯告诉你吗？
Did Iris tell you about it?
她说了什么？
What did she say?
好吧，她说了什么吗？
Okay, did she say anything?
也许如果我能和她说话...
Maybe if I could talk to her...
与谁交谈？
Talk to who?
斯蒂芬正在梦见艾里斯奶奶。
Steph is dreaming about Grandma Iris.
Psycho Granny？
Psycho granny?
我以为她死了。
I thought she was dead.
好吧，她对我们死了。
Well, she's dead to us.
斯蒂芬妮（Stephanie），艾里斯·坎贝尔（Iris Campbell）是一位受到深深不安的女人。
Stephanie, Iris Campbell is a very deeply disturbed woman.
看，如果我能和她交谈，那么也许我可以让这些梦想停止。
Look, if I could just talk to her, then maybe I can get these dreams to stop.
斯蒂芬，只需放下它。
Steph, just drop it.
我不明白。
I don't get it.
发生了什么事吗？
What happened that was so bad?
一方面，她是你母亲如此搞砸的原因。
For one thing, she's the reason that your mother's so screwed up.
什么？
What?
看，我只是不想再谈论这个了，好吗？
Look, I just don't want to talk about this anymore, okay?
霍华德叔叔，我只需要知道。
Uncle Howard, please, I just need to know.
看，斯蒂芬妮，我们父亲去世后，艾里斯（Iris）只是抢购了。
Look, Stephanie, after our father died, Iris just snapped.
她不会让我们上学。
She wouldn't let us go to school.
她把我们锁在房子里。
She locked us inside the house.
她着迷于我们死亡的所有可怕方式。
She obsessed about all the horrific ways we could die.
最终它变得如此糟糕，我的意思是如此糟糕，
And eventually it got so bad, I mean so bad,
国家进来，他们带你的母亲和我离开了她。
that the state came in and they took your mother and I away from her.
但这还没有结束。
But it didn't end there.
她通过寄养护理跟踪我们，当孩子出生时，
She tracked us all through foster care, and when the kids were born,
她开始向我们发送这些可怕的信，
she started sending us these horrible letters,
充满了ob告和这些令人不安的尸体照片。
that were full of obituaries and these disturbing pictures of dead bodies.
我们必须移动，这样她就不能再与我们联系了。
We had to move so she couldn't contact us anymore.
所以，呃，您还有这些字母吗？
So, uh, do you still have any of those letters?
不。
No.
我...
I...
斯蒂芬妮，听我说。
Stephanie, listen to me.
那个女人是一个生病和危险的人。
That woman is a sick and dangerous person.
为了您的幸福和安全，请远离她。
And for your well-being and your safety, stay the hell away from her.
我相信你。
I believe you.
我找到了Paco！
I found Paco!
我敢肯定，他现在很想在客厅里。
I'm sure he'd love to be in the living room right now.
来吧，伙计们。
Come on, guys.
他是怎么进入那里的？
How did he ever get in there?
我需要你帮助我。
I need you to help me.
你听到了你的叔叔。
You heard your uncle.
只是放开。
Just let it go.
你不明白。
You don't understand.
由于这个梦想，我的一生都在崩溃。
My whole life is falling apart because of this dream.
不仅如此，我觉得自己正在失去理智。
And not only that, I feel like I'm losing my mind.
拜托，您是唯一可以帮助我的人。
Please, you are the only person who can help me.
如果我与艾里斯（Iris）保持联系，霍华德将永远不会原谅我。
Howard would never forgive me if I put you in touch with Iris.
请。
Please.
无论您做什么，都不要在餐厅橱柜的底部抽屉里看。
Whatever you do, do not look in the bottom drawer of the dining room cabinet.
嗨，嗯，我在这里见Iris Campbell。
Hi, um, I'm here to see Iris Campbell.
您没有看到迹象吗？
Did you not see the signs?
呃，呃，是的，是的，我做到了。
Uh, uh, yeah, yes, I did.
然后把他妈的在这里。
Then get the fuck out of here.
我是你的孙女。
I'm your granddaughter.
斯蒂芬妮，清空口袋。
Stephanie, empty your pockets.
电话，钥匙，一切。
Phone, keys, everything.
好吧，我并不危险。
Well, I'm not dangerous.
我不是你怕你。
It's not you I'm afraid of.
嗯。
Uh.
慢慢进来。
Come in slowly.
关闭门。
Shut the door.
快速，快速，快速。
Quick, quick, quick.
不要移动。
Don't move.
我的天啊。
Oh my god.
真的是你。
It really is you.
我可以在你里面看到你的母亲。
I can see your mother in you.
嗨，一个。
Hi, um.
停下来，停下来。
Stop, stop.
不要移动。
Don't move.
直到我告诉你。
Not until I tell you.
试图欺骗我，不是吗？
Trying to trick me, aren't you?
让我放下警卫。
Getting me to let my guard down.
我。
I.
你去。
There you go.
跑步。
Run.
坐。
Sit.
好吧，一个。
Okay, um.
就是这样。
That's it.
所以。
So.
达琳怎么样？
How is Darlene?
你妈妈？
Your mom?
好的。
Okay.
嗯，不，我不知道。
Uh, no, I don't know.
我十岁的时候就离开了。
She left when I was ten.
所以我们不再看到她了。
So we don't see her anymore.
哦。
Oh.
但是你看到了我的来信。
But you saw my letters.
那就是为什么你在这里，对吗？
That's why you're here, right?
不。
No.
一。
Um.
我实际上是在这里，因为我一直在梦见天空。
I'm actually here because I've been dreaming about the sky view.
是的。
Yeah.
是的，在过去两个月中的每个晚上，这是同一梦想。
Yeah, every single night for the past two months it's the same dream.
在其中，您正在约会，但是舞池破裂，然后发生爆炸，然后您跌倒并死亡。
In it, you're on a date but then the dance floor breaks and then there's an explosion and then you fall and die.
是的。
Yeah.
是的，每个人都死了。
Yeah, everyone dies.
这不仅仅是你的梦想。
It wasn't just your dream.
这是我的预感。
It was my premonition.
几年前，在天空的视野中，我瞥见了未来，看到了即将发生的死亡。
Years ago at the sky view I got a glimpse into the future and saw what death was about to do.
嘿，不要扔那一分钱。
Hey, don't throw that penny.
你可以杀死一个人。
You could kill somebody.
哦，我很抱歉。
Oh, I'm so sorry.
当然。
Of course.
过去的两年绝对是神奇的，仅此而已。
These past two years have been absolutely magical and that's all because of you.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
这是不对的。
This isn't right.
那不是吗？
Is that a no?
每个人都会死。
Everyone's going to die.
整个建筑物都会下降。
The whole building is going to come down.
你是认真的？
Are you serious?
一分钱。
The penny.
虹膜？
Iris?
给我。
Give it to me.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
你他妈的怎么了？
What the fuck is wrong with you?
虹膜？
Iris?
那天晚上我挽救了很多生命。
I saved a lot of lives that night.
他们本来应该被保存。
They were meant to be saved.
之后他们关闭了餐厅。
They closed the restaurant after that.
说需要其他翻新。
Said it needed additional renovations.
但是它从未重新开放。
But it never reopened.
最终，他们将其拆除。
Eventually they tore it down.
所以你停止了灾难？
So you stopped the disaster?
是的。
Yes.
但是当您操他的计划时，死亡不喜欢它。
But death doesn't like it when you fuck with his plans.
因此，多年来，他回来了，他杀死了那天晚上在那里的所有人。
So over the years he came back and he killed everyone who was there that night.
包括我的保罗。
Including my Paul.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
你说死亡回来了吗？
Did you say death came back?
他是bit子的无情儿子。
He's a relentless son of a bitch.
直到他完成工作才停止。
Won't stop till he finishes the job.
但是我自学了如何看到他来。
But I taught myself how to see him coming.
预见他的一举一动。
To anticipate his every move.
多年来一直将他留在海边。
Been keeping him at bay for years now.
现在他有我。
And now he's got me.
癌症。
Cancer.
哦。
Oh.
相信那屎吗？
Believe that shit?
对不起。
Sorry.
两个月前得到了诊断。
Got the diagnosis two months ago.
等待。
Wait.
那是我开始做梦的时候。
That's when I started having my dream.
看？
See?
这是一个迹象。
It's a sign.
好的，但是为什么我梦见您所看到的呢？
Okay, but why am I dreaming about what you saw?
也许我的癌症将我的预感传给了您。
Maybe my cancer passed my premonition on to you.
也许这是命运的幽默感。
Maybe it's fate's demented sense of humor.
谁知道谁？
Who the hell knows?
重要的是，当宇宙说话时，您会注意。
What matters is that when the universe speaks you pay attention.
我看到你，你他妈的。
I see you, you fuck.
嗯？
Huh?
一。
Um.
你在跟谁说话？
Who are you talking to?
死亡。
Death.
他认为我分心是因为你在这里。
He thinks I'm distracted because you're here.
我必须教你本书中的一切。
I have to teach you everything in this book.
学习基础知识将需要一些时间。
It'll take some time to learn the basics.
因此，您需要留在这里。
So you'll need to stay here.
呆在这里？
Stay here?
外界太危险了。
The outside world is too dangerous.
我二十年来还没有走到那里。
I haven't stepped out there in twenty years.
在这里，我们可以安全。
In here, we can be safe.
哦。
Oh.
看到吗？
See that?
是的。
Yeah.
这就是我的所有研究。
This is all my research.
我一生的工作。
My life's work.
看，对不起。
Look, I'm sorry.
我不能。
I can't.
我不能呆在这里。
I can't stay here.
我必须回到学校，但是，你知道，我会回来的，我会去。
I have to get back to school, but, you know, I'll come back and I'll visit.
不！
No!
我生病了！
I'm sick!
我不会那么长。
I won't be alive that long.
你不能离开。
You can't leave.
你不明白吗？
Don't you see?
我们的家人即将到来。
Death is coming for our family.
你不相信我吗？
You don't believe me?
不。
No.
我想我犯了一个错误。
I think I made a mistake.
我认为这可能只是一个梦。
I think it was probably just a dream.
不，等等！
No, wait!
至少拿书！
At least take the book!
这本书是生命线。
This book is a lifeline.
它将向您展示您需要知道的一切，以确保我们的家庭安全。
It will show you everything you need to know to keep our family safe.
你仍然不相信我吗？
You still don't believe me?
退后一步。
Step back.
看到是相信的。
Seeing is believing.
嘿，斯蒂芬。
Hey, Steph.
她的脸真的在你面前爆炸。
Her face really exploded right in front of you.
嘿！
Hey!
只是别管她。
Just leave her alone.
斯蒂芬，这是我的糟糕。
It's my bad, Steph.
我只是好奇。
I'm just curious.
嘿。
Hey.
你如何举起？
How are you holding up?
抱歉，叔叔帮助了。
Sorry Uncle helped.
你对我们的正确。
You were right about ours.
我永远不应该去过那里。
I never should have went there.
亲爱的，无需道歉。
Honey, there's no need to apologize.
很抱歉，您必须经历。
I'm so sorry you had to go through that.
她死前对我说了些什么。
She said something to me before she died.
她说，我们的家人即将死亡。
She said death was coming for our family.
太疯狂了，对吧？
That's crazy, right?
我简直不敢相信。
I can't believe it.
我给她发了电子邮件。
I emailed her.
我只是不认为她会出现。
I just didn't think she'd show up.
快点。
Come on.
那是妈妈吗？
Is that Mom?
是的。
Yeah.
真的吗？
Really?
哇。
Wow.
不要荒谬。
Don't be ridiculous.
快点。
Come on.
到这里。
Get down here.
来这里。
Come here.
欢迎来到烧烤。
Welcome to the barbecue.
斯蒂芬。
Steph.
如果她要去霍华德叔叔的家，那我就不是。
If she's going to Uncle Howard's house, then I'm not.
你可以和爸爸一起兜风。
You can get a ride with Dad.
你甚至都不会和她说话吗？
You're not even going to talk to her?
快点。
Come on.
你不像我那样记得她。
You don't remember her like I do.
只是给她一个机会。
Just give her a chance.
为什么？
Why?
查理，她抛弃了我们，现在她滚来了吗？
Charlie, she abandoned us and now she rolls in here?
这些年来，想做什么都没发生？
After all these years and wants to act like nothing happened?
因为谁会这样做，对吧？
Because who would do that, right?
等等，什么？
Wait, what?
没有什么。
Nothing.
不。
No.
那应该是什么意思？
What's that supposed to mean?
我尝试打电话给你很多次，什么也没有。
I tried calling you so many times and nothing.
与朱莉娅一样。
Same with Julia.
您曾经是最好的朋友。
You used to be best friends.
你甚至不再说话了。
You don't even talk anymore.
好的。
Okay.
好吧，对不起。
Well, I'm sorry.
由于这个和这场噩梦，我刚刚分散了过去几个月的注意力。
I've just been distracted the last couple of months because of this and this nightmare.
那之前呢？
What about before that?
自从您离开以来一直这样。
It's been like this ever since you left.
你对妈妈生气，但你也没有来。
You're mad at Mom, but you haven't been around either.
我不喜欢她。
I'm not like her.
好的？
Okay?
我不是疯了。
I'm not crazy.
不，你是对的。
No, you're right.
你不是疯了。
You're not crazy.
好的。
Okay.
你只是不在乎。
You just don't care.
现在您明白了，请注意碎片。
Now you got it, watch out for splinters.
嘿，她是。
Hey, there she is.
嘿。
Hey.
来这里。
Come here.
我很高兴你做到了。
I'm so glad you made it.
当然。
Of course.
进来。
Come on in.
嘿，大家。
Hey, everybody.
快点。
Come on.
来吧。
Come on over.
我做了饼干。
I made cookies.
那太棒了。
That's great.
我可以尝试一个吗？
Can I try one?
是的当然。
Yes, of course.
这有花生酱吗？
Does this have peanut butter?
是的。
Yeah.
你要杀死我的兄弟吗？
Are you trying to kill my brother?
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
鲍勃过敏。
Bob is allergic.
是的。
Yeah.
我完全忘记了。
I totally forgot.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
重要的是你在这里。
The important thing is that you're here.
所以，鲍比调酒师，喝酒。
So, Bobby Bartender, drinks.
周围喝酒。
Drinks all around.
家庭。
Family.
您不会选择自己得到的那个。
You don't get to pick the one you get.
您只需要爱自己得到的那个。
You just got to love the one that you got.
现在，我们的母亲，她独自生活直到她去世的那一天。
Now, our mother, she lived alone until the day that she died.
她的死应该提醒我们所有人享受生活，
And her death should be a reminder to all of us to enjoy life,
并花时间我们在一起，因为我们不会回来。
and spend the time that we have together because we're not going to get any back.
我爱你们。
I love you guys.
干杯。
Cheers.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
那里有一个错误。
There's a bug in there.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
我得到了它。
I got it.
- 我想，你明白了。 - 只是看。
- I think, you got it. - Just watch.
- 我正在尝试找到一份新工作。 - 那太棒了！
- I'm trying to get a new job. - That's great!
查理！
Charlie!
在这里起床。
Get up here.
你要我加入你吗？
Do you want me to join you?
很高兴见到你。
Good to see you.
您在这里的设置。
The setup you've got here.
好吧，我希望孩子们度过一个快乐的童年，与我认识的一些人不同。
Well, I wanted the kids to have a happy childhood unlike some people I know.
您不是在谈论我们，是吗？
You're not talking about us, are you?
哦，不。
Oh, no.
我们的童年很棒。
We had a great childhood.
看着我。
Look at me.
我原来很棒。
I turned out fabulous.
是的。
Yep.
霍华德。
Howard.
那是什么？
What is that?
它看起来像是房子钥匙。
It looks like a house key.
快点。
Come on.
你知道，我们有备用房间，
You know, we got the spare room,
而且，它比在拖车公园周围弹跳要好。
and it's got to be better than bouncing around trailer parks.
我认为这不是一个好主意。
I don't think this is a good idea.
第二次机会永远不会太晚。
It's never too late for a second chance.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
没有我，他们会更好。
They're better off without me.
捡起。
Pick up.
快点。
Come on.
你告诉我，好吗？
You got to me, all right?
你去找我。
You got to me.
嘿，伙计们，来告诉我们您的背部翻转。
Hey, guys, come show us your back flip.
什么？
What?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
是的，来吧，霍华德叔叔。
Yeah, come on, Uncle Howard.
来吧，霍华德。
Come on, Howard.
霍华德。
Howard.
哦，是的。
Oh, yeah.
你去。
There you go.
好吧，我们去。
All right, here we go.
提防。
Watch out.
等待，停下来！
Wait, stop!
好接球，安迪。
Nice catch, Andy.
好吧，我们走了。
Alright, here we go.
来吧，霍华德。
Come on, Howard.
开始了。
Here we go.
小心，霍华德！
Careful, Howard!
斯蒂芬妮。
Stephanie.
我很高兴您决定来。
I'm glad you decided to come.
现在整个家庭在这里！
Now the whole family's here!
我还好。
I'm okay.
好吧。
Alright.
好的。
Good.
他将擦去他们眼睛的每一滴眼泪。
And he shall wipe away every tear from their eyes.
这些东西是什么？
What is all this stuff?
好的。
Okay.
我在虹膜书中找到了这些论文。
I found these papers in Iris' book.
他们是在Skyview的人们的ob告和文章
They are obituaries and articles for the people who were at the Skyview,
在艾里斯（Iris）预见的那天晚上。
on the night that Iris had her premonition.
这些人中的每个人都以一些怪异而混乱的方式死亡。
Each one of these people went on to die in some weird and messed up way.
不仅如此，他们都以与艾里斯（Iris）的预感相同的顺序去世。
And not only that, they all died in the same order as Iris' premonition.
那天晚上，数百人应该死亡，但艾里斯（Iris）停止了这场灾难。
Hundreds of people were supposed to die that night, but Iris stopped the disaster.
因此，死亡为他们一个一个一个。
So, death came back for them one by one.
由于幸存者这么多，因此死亡花了数年的时间才能到达所有人。
Since there were so many survivors, it took years for death to get to all of them.
但是最终它到了艾里斯。
But eventually it got to Iris.
我的意思是，她是预见中最后一个死亡的人。
I mean, she was the last to die in the premonition.
是她和一个小男孩。
It was her and a little boy.
但是她已经准备好了。
But she was prepared.
她单枪匹马地停留了数十年。
She single-handedly held off death for decades.
斯蒂芬妮，亲爱的。
Stephanie, sweetie.
我认为这不是一个适当的时间。
I don't think this is the appropriate time for this.
是的，我的意思是，这甚至与我们有任何关系，对吗？
Yeah, I mean, none of this even has anything to do with us, right?
我们为什么在这里？
Why are we even here?
它与我们有关。
It has everything to do with us.
因为死亡花了很长时间才能通过幸存者，所以这些人继续有家人。
Because death took so long to make its way through the survivors, these people went on to have families.
他们永远不应该拥有的家庭。
Families that they never should have had.
所以死亡也带走了他们。
So death took them too.
你看不到吗？
Don't you see this?
我们的死亡来了，因为我们永远都不应该存在。
Death is coming for us because we were never supposed to exist.
好吧，为什么这个房间里的每个人都在死亡的热门名单上？
Okay, so why everybody in this room is on death's hit list?
鲍比，医生，这就是她的意思。
Bobby, Doc, that's what she's saying.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
爸爸和布伦达姨妈是安全的，因为它们不是艾里斯血统的一部分。
Dad and Aunt Brenda are safe because they're not part of Iris' bloodline.
好的。
Okay.
遵循模式，死亡按年龄逐渐降低了每个分支。
Following the pattern, death makes its way down each branch by age.
因此，由于霍华德叔叔是最古老的，所以它将首先从他的家人开始，意思是埃里克，你是下一个。
So because Uncle Howard was the oldest, it'll start with his family first, meaning Eric, you're next.
去他妈的自己。
Go fuck yourself.
然后，朱莉娅（Julia）然后是鲍比（Bobby）。
Then it'll go for Julia, then Bobby.
然后，它将从达琳（Darlene）开始，然后是我，然后是查理（Charlie）。
Then it'll come for our branch, starting with Darlene, then me, then Charlie.
查理。
Charlie.
你买这个吗？
You buying this?
我不知道。
I don't know.
这太混乱了。
This is so messed up.
我的意思是，您将父亲的死变成了某种性交的阴谋论。
I mean, you're turning our dad's death into some kind of fucked up conspiracy theory.
你怎么了？
What is wrong with you?
不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no.
不是，这不是阴谋论。
It's not, it's not a conspiracy theory.
就足够了。
That's enough.
我们都会死。
We're all gonna die.
停止！
Stop!
我再也听不到一分钟的话了。
I can't listen to this for one more minute.
那个疯女人的胡说八道给这个家庭造成了足够的痛苦和痛苦。
That crazy woman's nonsense has caused enough pain and suffering for this family.
不挂断。
Hang on.
布伦达姨妈，请别管它。
Aunt Brenda, please just leave it alone.
好的，在艾里斯（Iris）的书中，她提到了一个欺骗死亡并幸存下来的人。
Okay, in Iris' book, she mentions somebody who cheated death and survived.
斯蒂芬妮。
Stephanie.
埃里克（Eric），不，等等。
Eric, no, wait.
我担心你。
I'm worried about you.
停止它。
Stop it.
我会照顾好这个。
I'll be taking care of this.
来吧，鲍比。
Come on, Bobby.
布伦达。
Brenda.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
不，不，不，你不能。
No, no, no, you can't.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
请。
Please.
你相信我，对吗？
You believe me, right?
对不起。
I'm sorry.
朱莉娅。
Julia.
看，我爱你。
Look, I love you.
但是有时候我真的很讨厌你。
But sometimes I really hate you.
我知道。
I know.
我知道所有这些都有多么令人信服，但这不是真实的。
I know how convincing all of this can be, but it's not real.
你怎么说？
How can you say that?
我知道艾里斯教你所有这一切。
I know Iris taught you all of this.
不要让我妈妈的信念像我的生活方式一样使您的生活脱轨。
Don't let my mom's beliefs derail your life the same way they did mine.
非常感谢您的建议，但我真的不再需要妈妈了。
Thank you so much for that advice, but I really don't need a mom anymore.
好的，宽阔。
All right, open wide.
非常好。
Very good.
只是要捏。
Just gonna pinch hard.
准备好？
Ready?
五个，四个，三个，两个。
Five, four, three, two.
好工作。
Good job.
我要去俱乐部。
I'm gonna hit the club.
我需要你锁定。
I need you to lock up.
而且不要碰我的酒。
And don't touch any of my liquor.
不，不，您什么都没说锁定。
No, no, you didn't say anything about locking up.
是的，是的。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我没有说关闭，伙计。
I didn't say shit about closing, dude.
哭我一条河。
And cry me a river.
我希望你在地狱里燃烧。
I hope you burn in hell.
你相信那屎吗？
You believe that shit?
我的老人刚刚去世。
My old man just died.
我进来是为了对那个混蛋的帮助，现在他要我锁定。
I come in as a favor to that asshole, and now he wants me to lock up.
你知道那是什么吗？
You know what that is?
这是不考虑的。
It's inconsiderate.
无论如何，你们都完成了。
Anyway, you're all done.
谢谢。
Thank you.
嘿，五星级评论，是吗？
Hey, five-star review, yeah?
喜欢并订阅和所有东西。
Like and subscribe and all the things.
不，我不会忘记今天晚上或你离开时你的脸，但是
No, I can't forget this evening or your face as you were leaving, but
我想这就是故事的发展方式。
I guess that's just the way the story goes.
现在，我应该让您知道您应该知道的只是公平的。
And now it's only fair that I should let you know what you should know.
我不能活着，如果没有你的话。
I can't live, if living is without you.
我不能给。
I can't give.
我不能再说了。
I can't give anymore.
上帝该死。
God dammit.
查理，醒来。
Charlie, wake up.
我一直在试图整夜打电话给埃里克。
I've been trying to call Eric all night.
他没有回答我。
He's not answering me.
我不知道他在哪里。
I don't know where he is.
我很担心。
I'm worried.
我确定他很好。
I'm sure he's fine.
好吧，你收到他的来信了吗？
Well, have you heard from him?
我要去那儿。
I'm going over there.
我需要检查他。
I need to check on him.
你也要来，查理。
You're coming too, Charlie.
我认为他去了语音邮件。
I think he's gone to voicemail.
那是他吗？
Is that him?
我的朋友刚刚设置了昨晚的测试记录器燃烧。
My friend just set the test recorder to burn down last night.
什么？
What?
斯蒂芬，斯蒂芬！
Steph, Steph!
哇！
Ow!
埃里克？
Eric?
哦，是的，不，当然是你。
Oh, yeah, no, of course it's you.
伙计！
Dude!
我们听说了大火。
We heard about the fire.
我们以为你死了。
We thought you were dead.
我很好。
I'm fine.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我很担心你。
I'm so worried about you.
是的，他妈的。
Yeah, fuck.
火说我很幸运，我穿着那套皮夹克。
Fire said I was lucky as fuck that I was wearing that leather jacket.
几乎没有被烧毁。
Barely got burned.
真的，我最喜欢的外套。
Really my favorite jacket, though.
这是什么？
What is this?
哦，是的，请检查一下。
Oh, yeah, check it out.
我有品牌。
I got branded.
生病了，对吗？
Sick, right?
你喜欢吗？
You like it?
你说你睡着了。
You said you were asleep.
您正在像个该死的缠扰者一样炸毁我的手机。
You're blowing up my phone like a goddamn stalker.
你要我做什么？
What do you want me to do?
不，我不明白。
No, I don't get it.
你应该死。
You should be dead.
是的，是的。
Right, yeah, yeah.
或者，也许...
Or, you know, maybe...
也许死亡实际上并不是我们的家人来的。
Maybe death's not actually coming for our family.
因为那会疯了。
Because that would be fucking crazy.
耶稣屎！
Jesus shit!
也许我是无敌的。
Or maybe I'm invincible.
埃里克？
Eric?
埃里克！
Eric!
是的？
Yeah?
埃里克，等等。
Eric, wait.
停止。
Stop.
等一下，好吗？
Just wait, okay?
仅仅因为昨晚死亡没有杀死您，并不意味着您安全。
Just because death didn't kill you last night doesn't mean that you're safe.
远离那树修剪器！
Stay away from that tree trimmer!
哦。
Ooh.
斯蒂芬会自己搬家吗？
Gonna move on its own, Steph?
那将要做什么？
Is that what it's gonna do?
它可能会倒下。
It could fall.
并远离这些孩子。
And stay away from these kids.
我会抓住机会。
I'll take my chances.
斯蒂芬，几个孩子和足球的孩子怎么会杀死他？
Steph, how's a couple kids with a soccer ball gonna kill him?
我的意思是，我不知道。
I mean, I don't know.
修剪器可能会跌落并击中叶吹制的家伙，
The trimmer could fall and hit the leaf blower guy,
这导致他将东西吹到孩子的眼睛中，然后将球带入他的脸上。
which causes him to blow stuff into the kids' eyes and then take the ball into his face.
哇，哇，哇，哇。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
足球在我的脸上？
Soccer ball in my face?
听起来确实是致命的。
That does sound deadly.
我应该更加小心。
I should be more careful.
嘿！
Hey!
这是怎么回事？
What's up?
你怎么了？
What happened to you?
死亡。
Charbroiled by death.
埃里克，吧？
Eric, huh?
基基，那很糟糕。
Kiki, that was pretty bad.
哦，等等，让我看看。
Oh, wait, let me see that.
埃里克（Eric），远离卡车。
Eric, just stay away from the truck.
哦，什么？
Oh, what?
这卡车？
This truck?
停止！
Stop!
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
请。
Please.
这辆卡车在这里吗？
This truck right here?
但这真是一辆美丽的卡车！
But it's such a beautiful truck!
停止！
Stop!
不要碰！
Don't touch it!
埃里克，等等！
Eric, just wait!
停止！
Stop!
你喜欢吗？
You like that?
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
哦！
Uh-oh!
埃里克（Eric）再次测试死亡！
Eric's testing death again!
会发生什么？
What's gonna happen?
停止这样做！
Stop doing that!
会发生什么？
What's gonna happen?
那呢？
How about that?
我只是想帮助您。
I'm just trying to help you.
好的。
Okay.
老实说，我们的垃圾已经完成了。
Honestly, we're so done with your garbage.
你能...
Can you please...
在第1500次，没有人对您愚蠢的小死亡诅咒感到不安，好吗？
For the 1500th time, no one gives a shit about your stupid little death curse, okay?
因此，请提示并让我们独自一人，因为我们的家人没有死亡。
So take a hint and leave us alone, because death's not coming for our family.
哇！
Whoa!
斯蒂芬应该相信你。
Should've believed you, Steph.
不，我，嗯...
No, I, uh...
我把命令搞砸了，现在朱莉娅死了。
I screwed up the order, and now Julia's dead.
这是我的错。
It's my fault.
发生的事情是创伤和糟糕的。
What happened was traumatic and awful.
这不是你的错。
It's not your fault.
这是我的错。
It's my fault.
好吧，这不是你的错。
Well, it's not your fault.
这是我的错。
It is my fault.
斯蒂芬妮，您对订单只是错误的，因为有一些您不应该知道的东西。
Stephanie, you were only wrong about the order, because there's something you shouldn't know.
埃里克不是霍华德的亲生儿子。
Eric isn't Howard's biological son.
对不起，你在说什么？
I'm sorry, what are you talking about?
而且，斯蒂芬妮，我不相信你，所以我什么也没对你说什么，现在我的小女孩死了。
And, Stephanie, I didn't believe you, so I didn't say anything to you, and now my little girl's dead.
好吧，我不明白你为什么有外遇。
Well, I don't understand why you had an affair.
你和你的父亲和我经历了这么困难。
You and your father and I were having such a hard time.
但这很好，因为我得到了你。
But it was good, because I got you.
我让你摆脱了。
I got you out of it.
我要读这读，但我会读的。
I was gonna read that, but I'm just gonna read that.
没关系，因为霍华德如此爱你，这么多。
It doesn't matter, because Howard loved you so, so much.
是谁？
Who is it?
谁在这一切周围？
Who's been around all that?
杰拉德·芬伯里（Gerard Fenbury）。
Gerard Fenbury.
哦！
Oh!
杰拉德·芬伯里（Gerard Fenbury）？
Gerard Fenbury?
是的。
Yes.
妈的。
Oh, shit.
不，不，不，不！
No, no, no, no!
杰拉德他妈的芬伯里？
Gerard fucking Fenbury?
您不知道我们正在经历什么。
You don't know what we're going through.
哦，上帝。
Oh, God.
这就是为什么您一直想打球的原因？
What, is this why you always wanted to play catch?
哦。
Oh.
好的。
Okay.
因此，这意味着，如果它以正确的顺序进行，那么我下一步，对吧？
So, that means that if it's going in the right order, then I'm next, right?
你必须帮我，斯蒂芬。
You gotta help me, Steph.
我认为我不能。
I don't think that I can.
我的意思是，我以为我做到了，但我没有...
I mean, I thought I did, but I don't...
不，但是你可以。
No, but you can.
我的意思是，您确切地预测了将会发生的事情。
I mean, you predicted exactly what was gonna happen.
您只是犯了错误，因为您没有所有信息，查理。
You just got the order wrong, because you didn't have all the information, Charlie.
预测，你是什么意思？
What do you mean, predicted?
她看到了一切。
She saw everything.
修剪器，鼓风机，足球，就像...
The trimmer, the blower, the soccer ball, like...
就像有一个难题，她只需要把它们放在一起，你知道我的意思吗？
It was like there were pieces to a puzzle, and she just had to put them together, you know what I mean?
是真的吗？
Is that true?
亲爱的，请不要鼓励这个。
Darling, please, do not encourage this.
马蒂，我的意思是...
Marty, I mean...
我的意思是，这是虹膜书中的一切，这是...
I mean, it's everything in Iris' book, it's...
就像，就像一个方程式一样，是数学。
It's like, it's like an equation, it's math.
斯蒂芬妮，如果您可以看到所有这些如何合并在一起，我们可能会有机会。
Stephanie, if you can see how all of this fits together, we might have a chance.
斯蒂芬，当您走出去时，您摧毁了这个家庭，但是没有您，我们还可以。
Steph, you devastated this family when you walked out, but we've been okay without you.
我恳求您不要再创伤我们的孩子了。
I'm begging you not to traumatize our kids anymore.
这次是真实的。
It's real this time.
我要散步。
I'm going for a walk.
我可以欣赏我们的家人将来需要一些咨询，但是...
I can appreciate that our family is clearly gonna need some counseling in the future, but...
我们可以专注于我们要死的事实，对吗？
can we focus on the fact that we're all about to die, right?
我是说...
I mean...
我的意思是，斯蒂芬，你不是说艾里斯认识一个欺骗死亡之类的人吗？
I mean, Steph, didn't you say that Iris knew someone that cheated death or something?
是的，嗯...
Yeah, um...
就在这里，它说...
Right here, somewhere, it says...
那，嗯...
That, um...
就在这里。
Right here.
JB找到了一个幸存的人，但对此JB是谁，这并没有说什么。
J.B. found someone who survived, but it doesn't say anything about who this J.B. was or...
等一下，我知道那个名字。
Wait a minute, I know that name.
我妈妈曾经给我写信，
My mom used to write me letters,
她有时会谈论她的一个名叫JB的朋友，他在医院工作。
and she sometimes would talk about a friend of hers named J.B. who worked at a hospital.
一...
Um...
嗯，某事，呃，河道医院，嗯，呃，深河，呃，和平河医院，呃，清晰...
Um, something, uh, something river hospital, uh, uh, deep river, uh, peace river hospital, uh, clear...
希望，希望河？
Hope, Hope River?
就是这样！
That's it!
该死，就像一个小时的路程。
Shit, it's like an hour away.
我要去。
I'm going.
我要去找他自己说话。
I'm gonna go find him and talk to him myself.
好吧，我和你一起去。
Well, I'm coming with you.
就是这样，好吧，是的，让我们走吧。
That's it, okay, yeah, yeah, let's, let's go.
奥兹，我...
Ozzy, I...
什么？
What?
您需要和妈妈一起呆在这里并拯救她。
You need to stay here with your mom and save her.
是的，操，你在跟我开玩笑吗？
Yeah, fuck that, are you kidding me?
我不是一个人呆在这里。
I'm not staying here by myself.
这对您来说太危险了，你不能...
It's too dangerous on the road for you, you can't...
不，我读了Gammy的死书，好吧，好吗？
No, I read Gammy's death book, okay, alright?
我的意思是，伙计，那件事上有一千个与房屋有关的死亡。
I mean, there's like a thousand house-related deaths in that thing, man.
你沿着楼梯绊倒，跌倒...
You trip down the stairs, fall...
下厕所之类的东西，我不知道，但我不是，但我不是...
down a toilet or something, I don't, I don't know, but I'm not, I'm not...
没办法，我不呆在这里。
No way, I'm not staying here.
等等，挂断。
Hang on, hang on.
嘿，好吧，太快了。
Hey, okay, too fast.
好吧，好吧，我们会慢，我们会慢。
Okay, okay, we'll go slow, we'll go slow.
我要去打开卡车。
I'm gonna go open up the truck.
查理，检查背面。
Charlie, check the back.
知道了。
Got it.
请小心，有时这些步骤很滑。
Be careful, the steps are slippery sometimes.
嘿！
Oi!
你们中的任何一个混蛋都在做坚果检查吗？
Any of you fuckers doing nut check?
打扰一下？
Excuse me?
几天前，您用花生酱在其中用花生酱制作了饼干。
You made cookies in that thing with peanut butter in them just a few days ago.
这个可怜的混蛋甚至甚至触摸了坚果，他的喉咙都会紧紧地闭合，...
This poor bastard so much as even touches a nut, his throat is gonna close up tight and...
您知道，花生酱在哪里？
You understand, where's the peanut butter?
机舱和水槽附近。
Cabin and about the sink.
谢谢。
Thank you.
对不起，鲍比，我只是...
I'm so sorry, Bobby, I just...
嘿，好的。
Hey, okay.
一切都清晰。
All clear.
谢谢。
Thank you.
你是一个好兄弟，埃里克。
You're a good brother, Eric.
螺母检查。
Nut check.
什么？
What?
哦！
Oh!
上帝！
God!
哦！
Oh!
很好，我明白了。
It was good, I get it.
快点。
Come on.
只会变得更糟。
It's only getting worse.
该死。
Dammit.
等待！
Wait!
我和你一起去，兄弟。
I'm coming with you, bro.
有人必须保护你。
Someone's gotta protect you.
爸爸又打电话了？
Dad's calling, again?
告诉他，我们只是和妈妈一起兜风。
Tell him we just went for a ride with Mom.
他不会相信。
He's not gonna believe that.
至少它会给我们买一段时间。
At least it'll buy us some time.
时间？
Time?
死亡不会让我们死了。
Death doesn't get us your dead will.
我总是把它们留在我可以看到的地方。
I always keep them where I can see them.
我的意思是，您本来可以拥有真实的事情，但是没关系，并不是每个人都想成为妈妈。
I mean, you could've just had the real thing, but it's okay, not everyone wants to be a mom.
那是你的想法吗？
Is that what you think?
我不想成为妈妈吗？
That I don't wanna be a mom?
看，我是由一个女人抚养长大的，她教我到处看到死亡。
Look, I was raised by a woman who taught me to see death everywhere.
我以为我可以把它放在我身后，但是当我有你和你的兄弟时，
I thought I could put it behind me, but then when I had you and your brother,
我所能看到的是您和查理可能死的一百种不同的方式。
all I could see were a hundred different ways that you and Charlie could die.
我不想你离开家。
I didn't want you to leave the house.
我一无所获。
I would freak out on you guys over nothing.
有一天，我看着你的脸，我看到了我长大的同一个害怕的小女孩，
One day, I looked at your face, and I saw the same scared little girl that I was growing up,
我知道，如果我留下来，我会毁了你的生活。
and I knew that if I stayed, I was gonna ruin your life.
我不知道我做正确的事。
I have no idea if I did the right thing.
但是我现在在这里为你服务。
But I'm here for you now.
前台就是这样。
The front desk is this way.
嗨，嗯，我们正在寻找JB。
Hi, um, we're looking for JB.
你是谁？
And who are you?
前台告诉我们，我们可以在这里找到他，是你吗？
The front desk told us we could find him down here, is that you?
威廉·约翰·布洛沃斯（William John Bloodworth）。
William John Bloodworth.
但是我的朋友叫我JB。
But my friends call me JB.
我一直在等你，斯蒂芬妮。
I've been waiting for you, Stephanie.
查理。
Charlie.
所以，你们中的哪一个...
So, which one of you...
得知艾里斯，我很遗憾。
I was sorry to hear about Iris.
她是一个特别的女人。
She was a special woman.
你怎么认识她？
How did you know her?
她拯救了我的生命。
She saved my life.
什么时候？
When?
天空的视图。
The sky view.
那天晚上我去上班。
I went to work that night.
JB，亲爱的，我告诉过你，当我登上舞台时，你必须呆在那里。
JB, honey, I told you, you gotta stay back there while I'm on stage.
我不应该在那里。
I wasn't supposed to be there.
当然，除了死亡。
Except, of course, to die.
因此，一直以来，她不仅保护我们的家人，而且她也在保护您。
So all that time, she wasn't just protecting our family, she was protecting you too.
几年后，她追踪了我。
Years later, she tracked me down.
帮助我看到了真相。
Helped me see the truth.
我们交易了想法。
We traded ideas.
我帮助她加强了她的小屋。
I helped her fortify her cabin.
我们成为朋友。
We became friends.
考虑到她的病情，我什至帮助她获得了最好的医疗服务。
I even helped her get the best medical care I could, considering her condition.
艾里斯说，您发现有人停止死亡并幸存下来。
Iris said that you'd found somebody who stopped death and survived.
是的。
Yes.
我们该怎么做？
And how do we do that?
只有两种方法。
There are only two ways.
通过杀人或死亡。
By killing, or by dying.
如果您夺走生命，那么您就会有时间留下的时间。
If you take a life, you get the time that person had left.
什么？
What?
不，我不会杀人。
No, I'm not gonna kill someone.
也许我们应该让那个家伙结束。
Maybe we should let the guy finish.
然后，为了真正打破周期，您必须死亡。
Then to truly break the cycle, you have to die.
这意味着什么？
What does that mean?
很久以前，一个名叫金伯利·科尔曼（Kimberly Corman）的年轻女子像你一样，发现自己处于死亡名单上。
A long time ago, a young woman named Kimberly Corman found herself on death's list, just like you.
当她终于回来时，她死了。
And when her turn finally came, she died.
扁平。
Flatlined.
但是她的医生设法把她带回来，这打破了链条。
But her doctor managed to bring her back, and that broke the chain.
好吧，好吧，我们要这样做。
Well, alright then, we'll do that.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
虹膜为什么不尝试？
Why didn't Iris try that?
这是有风险的。
It's risky.
而且，如果您他妈的死亡并输了，事情可能会变得非常混乱。
And if you fuck with death and lose, things can get very messy.
等等，挂断。
Hang on, hang on.
好吧，等等。
Okay, wait.
必须有另一种方式。
There has to be another way.
拜托，您必须帮助我们。
Please, you have to help us.
多年来，人们一直向我寻求建议。
For years, people have been coming to me for advice.
好吧，我很累。
Well, I'm tired.
我已经完成了所有这些。
I'm done with all that.
现在我像Iris一样生病了。
And now I'm sick, just like Iris.
这次没有跑步。
There's no running this time.
事实是，你们都会死。
Fact is, you're all gonna die.
之后，我也会。
And after that, I will too.
现在我的老朋友走了，我要退休了。
Now that my old friend is gone, I'm retiring.
所以呢？
So what?
你只是要把我们留在这里吗？
You're just gonna leave us here?
我打算享受我离开的时间。
I intend to enjoy the time I have left.
我建议你也这样做。
And I suggest you do the same.
生活是宝贵的。
Life is precious.
享受每一秒。
Enjoy every single second.
你永远不知道什么时候。
You never know when.
太棒了。
That's fantastic.
不。
No.
不，不能。
No, that can't be it.
不。
No.
这里必须有一些东西。
There has to be something here.
必须还有另一个答案。
There has to be another answer.
他给了我们一个答案。
He gave us an answer.
鲍比（Bobby）必须死。
Bobby's gotta die.
埃里克！
Eric!
你他妈的疯了吗？
Are you fucking insane?
我们不是杀死鲍比。
We're not killing Bobby.
我是唯一听过那个家伙的人吗？
Am I the only guy that just listened to that dude?
只有一种方式。
There's only one way.
我们杀死了鲍比。
We kill Bobby.
我们使他振奋，然后繁荣，你们都脱离了死亡名单。
We resuscitate him, and then boom, you're all off death's list.
恭喜。
Congratulations.
必须还有其他东西，对吗？
There has to be something else, right?
我的意思是，必须有另一个解决方案，对，斯蒂芬吧？
I mean, there has to be another solution, right, Steph?
不。
No.
不，我们无能为力。
No, there's nothing else we can do.
好吧，结束了。
Okay, it's over.
嘿，你必须相信我，好吗？
Hey, you gotta trust me on this, okay?
她在放弃你。
She's giving up on you.
我不会去。
I'm not going to.
看，艾里斯（Iris）找到了几十年来阻止死亡的方法。
Look, Iris found a way to hold death off for decades.
我们也会。
So will we.
我相信那个家伙。
I trust that guy.
你相信那个家伙吗？
Do you trust that guy?
他很棒。
He was awesome.
他很有魅力，你也知道。
He was charismatic, and you know that as well.
埃里克（Eric）和鲍比（Bobby）走了。
Eric and Bobby are gone.
拉屎。
Shit.
拉屎！
Shit!
我不认为我喜欢这个。
I don't think I like this.
嘿，伙计，我们在医院里。
Hey, dude, we're in a hospital.
请记住，到处都有医生。
Remember, there's doctors everywhere.
我们杀了您，他们带您回来，每个人都安全。
We kill you, they bring you back, everybody's safe.
我们是英雄。
We're heroes.
从字面上看，这与确保您的安全相反。
That is literally the opposite of keeping you safe.
嗯？
Huh?
您想杀死某人并花时间离开吗？
You want to kill someone and take the time they have left?
如何？
How?
您甚至怎么知道他们有多少年？
How would you even know how many years they have?
不。
No.
好吧，我的意思是，不。
Well, I mean, no.
不，当然不是。
No, of course not.
不，我们永远不会。
No, we would never.
不要碰到那些婴儿。
Don't touch those babies.
看，底线，扁平线是您的最佳选择。
Look, bottom line, flatline is your best option.
你要失去什么？
What do you have to lose?
我们该怎么做？
How would we even do that?
看，我有一个主意。
See, I got an idea.
是的。
Yeah.
但这有点疯了。
But it's a little nuts.
您的过敏是致命的，对吗？
Your allergy is deadly, right?
出色地...
Well...
看，好吧，如果我出去的话，那不会是那种侮辱性的bit子，
Look, all right, if I'm going out, it's not going to be on those sort of insulted bitches,
好的？
all right?
给我那些。
Give me those.
不错的选择。
Nice choice.
哦，你必须在跟我开玩笑。
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
快点。
Come on.
嘿，好吧，来吧。
Hey, all right, come on.
你知道，也许这是一个标志，所以我们可以...
You know, maybe this is a sign so we can just...
哇！
Ow!
嘿，伙计，也许我们现在可以保释。
Hey, dude, maybe we can just bail now.
我没有放弃。
I'm not giving up.
你能帮忙吗？
Can you help?
没关系，我们在这里工作。
It's all right, we work here.
维护，很好。
Maintenance, it's fine.
戴上耳机。
Put your headphones back on.
杜德，它将倒下。
Dude, it's going to fall.
它将跌倒。
It's going to fall.
它跌倒了！
It's falling!
握住！
Hold it!
轻松的工作。
Easy work.
现在是什么？
Now what?
嘿，挂在这里。
Hey, hang here.
我必须得到一些东西。
I've got to get something.
不要移动。
Don't move.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
浴室在哪里？
Where's the bathroom?
他们不在房车中吗？
They weren't in the RV?
不。
No.
看，如果埃里克（Eric）试图削减鲍比（Bobby），它们会在哪里？
Look, if Eric was trying to cut Bobby, where would they be?
我不知道，但是有一百万个在医院死亡的方法。
I don't know, but there's a million ways to die in a hospital.
我可以帮你吗？
Can I help you?
打扰一下？
Excuse me?
不，只是...
No, just...
今天美好的一天。
Lovely day today.
还有很多时间？
Got much time left?
我希望如此。
I hope so.
所有属于人类设备的人才。
All the talent belonging to man devices there.
杜德，将汽车重新打开。
Dude, turn the car back on.
来吧，坐下。
Come on, sit down.
坐着，坐着，坐着。
Sit, sit, sit.
我马上回来。
I'll be right back.
嘿，您的Epipen在哪里？
Hey, where's your EpiPen?
就在这里。
It's right here.
给我。
Give it to me.
为什么？
Why?
那是什么？
What is that?
给它。
Give it.
听着，整个想法是你必须死。
Listen, the whole idea is that you have to die.
请记住，这使您活着。
Remember, this keeps you alive.
现在坐。
Now sit.
杜德，我们需要快点。
Dude, we need to hurry.
来吧，去。
Come on, go.
好吧，见面。
All right, meet up.
嘿，这个计划很棒，但是，您知道，如果它不起作用...
Hey man, the plan's great, but, you know, if it doesn't work out...
鲍比，它会起作用。
It's going to work, Bobby.
是的。
Yeah.
是的，但是，您知道，以防万一，我为真实而死，您愿意，嗯...
Yeah, but, you know, just in case, and I die for real, will you just, um...
您会照顾Paco吗？
Will you look after Paco?
是的，当然。
Yeah, yeah, of course.
杜德（Dude），我只是说，乌龟活到100岁，就像，看着我，看着我。
Dude, I'm just saying, turtles live to be like 100 years old, and it's like, look at me, look at me.
兄弟，我不会照顾Paco，因为您会没事的。
Brother, I'm not going to take care of Paco because you are going to be okay.
我和你，我们现在将为所有人修理问题。
Me and you, we are going to fix things for everyone, right now.
老实说，我不会让你死。
Honestly, I'm not going to let you die.
从技术上讲，我不会让你死，但是我要带你回来。
Technically, I'm not going to let you die, but then I'm going to bring you back.
快点。
Come on.
你明白了。
You got this.
我的天啊。
Oh my God.
什么？
What?
我知道这很好。
It's very good, I know.
所以呢？
So what?
好吧，除了好，你感觉什么？
Okay, other than good, what are you feeling?
没有什么。
Nothing.
你必须在跟我开玩笑。
You got to be kidding me.
什么，你告诉我你不再过敏了吗？
What, you're telling me you're not allergic anymore?
我不知道，伙计。
I don't know, man.
嘿，你在做。
Hey, you're doing it.
鲍比，你在做。
Bobby, you're doing it.
嘿，我和你在一起。
Hey, I'm here with you.
我和你在一起。
I'm here with you.
嘿，嘿，我不能给你。
Hey, hey, I can't give you that.
鲍比，鲍比。
Bobby, Bobby.
嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey.
等待。
Wait.
鲍比，只是去玩。
Bobby, just go for it and play.
鲍比，坐在轮椅上。
Bobby, in the wheelchair.
尝试再次打电话给他。
Try calling him again.
这是我们可以做到这一点的唯一方法。
This is the only way we can do this.
我的天啊。
Oh my God.
是的。
Yeah.
如果埃里克（Eric）与艾里斯（Iris）无关，为什么死了？
Why is Eric dead if he's not related to Iris?
当你和死亡他妈的时，事情变得凌乱。
When you fuck with death, things get messy.
我们必须离开这里。
We have to get out of here.
这不是安全的。
It's not safe.
去哪里？
And go where?
没有任何地方是安全的。
Nowhere is safe.
除了虹膜的小屋。
Except Iris' cabin.
她能够在那里生存数十年。
She was able to survive there for decades.
是的，然后她把脸吹了出来。
Yeah, and then she got her face blown off.
她只是因为离开机舱而死。
She only died because she left the cabin.
外部很危险，但里面是最安全的地方。
Outside is dangerous, but inside is the safest place that there is.
这是我们唯一具有任何优势的地方。
It's the only place where we have any advantage.
所以我们永远把自己锁在一个小屋中？
So we just lock ourselves in a cabin forever?
不是你。
Not you.
我。
Me.
妈妈，你不能离开。
Mom, you can't leave.
我们只是让你回来。
We just got you back.
如果有人要住在那个小屋里，那就是我。
If anybody's gonna live in that cabin, it's me.
只要我还活着，死亡就不会碰你。
And as long as I am alive, death can't touch you.
妈妈，让我这样做。
Mom, let me do this.
他永远不会让你独自到达那里。
He'll never let you get there on your own.
但是我可以看到他来了。
But I can see him coming.
我们必须一起做。
We have to do this together.
你更好。
You better.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
好的。
Okay.
你应该开车。
You should drive.
是的。
Yeah.
拉屎！
Shit!
看这个地方。
Look at this place.
不可能穿过那扇门。
It's gonna be impossible to get through that gate.
他即将采取行动。
He's about to make a move.
我不知道那是什么。
I don't know what it is.
我们现在需要带您进入。
We need to get you inside now.
等待。
Wait.
等等，什么？
Wait, what?
停止！
Stop!
好吧，让我们进去。
Okay, let's get inside.
射击！
Shoot!
什么？
What?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
不要等我。
Don't wait for me.
只是进去。
Just get inside.
斯蒂芬，如果您进去，我会很安全。
Steph, if you get inside, I'll be safe.
去。
Go.
好吧，来吧。
Okay, come on.
姐姐，我会救你。
I'll save you, sister.
我会尽可能地活着。
I'm gonna stay alive as long as I can.
查理。
Charlie.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
只是呼吸。
Just breathe.
呼吸。
Breathe.
查理，发生了什么事？
Charlie, what happened?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
你死了，我把你带回来。
You died, and I brought you back.
你把我带回来。
You brought me back.
我们现在很安全。
We're safe now.
妈妈。
Mom.
她救了我们。
She saved us.
妈妈。
Mom.
让我们回家。
Let's go home.
好吧，他在那里。
Well, there he is.
哇，好吧，查理。
Wow, okay, Charlie.
好的，给我们一个旋转。
All right, give us a spin.
你看起来真的很好。
You look really good.
我是一位出色的设计师。
I'm a great stylist.
来吧，我们会迟到。
Come on, we'll be late.
珍妮在哪里？
Where's Jenny?
我认为她还在里面，不是吗？
I think she's still inside, didn't we?
在这里，让我解决这个问题。
Here, let me fix this.
我真的很高兴您可以在这里为此。
I'm really happy you could be here for this.
我也是。
Me too.
哦。
Oh.
你好吗？
You okay?
是的。
Yeah.
请给我一个饼干吗？
Can I have one cookie, please?
谢谢。
Thank you.
斯蒂芬，我要你见珍妮的父亲雷迪克博士。
Steph, I want you to meet Jenny's dad, Dr. Reddick.
嘿，巴特，很高兴认识你。
Hey, Bart, nice to meet you.
你也是。
You too.
我们只是喜欢查理。
We just adore Charlie.
我知道他是救生员。
And I understand he's quite the lifesaver.
哦，是的，您听说过。
Oh, yeah, you heard about that.
他把我从死里复活。
He brought me back from the dead.
是的。
Yeah.
什么？
What?
好吧，从技术上讲，您还没有死。
Well, technically, you weren't dead.
什么？
What?
好吧，我的意思是，如果您失去知觉，而Charlie再次让您呼吸，
Well, I mean, if you were unconscious and Charlie got you breathing again,
那么你的心就没有停止。
then your heart didn't stop.
但是无论如何，查理。
But regardless, way to go, Charlie.
所以她还没死吗？
So she wasn't dead?
确切地。
Exactly.
她很幸运查理在那里。
She was lucky Charlie was there.
是的，一切都是有原因的。
Yeah, everything happens for a reason.
珍妮！
Jenny!
珍妮。
Jenny.
珍妮，你看起来像一百万美元。
Jenny, you look like a million bucks.
你好吗？
You okay?
跑步！
Run!
- 哦，天哪，那很近。 - 你还好吗？
- Oh my god, that was close. - Are you okay ?
是的。
Yeah.